Guide to the Records of the Washington Square Association, Inc. MC.94
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Activities
  - Greenwich Village Historic District Council, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square North Committee (Jan. - Apr.), 1950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square North Committee (May - Dec.), 1950 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square North Committee, 1951-52 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Landmarks: Historic Preservation, 1945-1949 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission (Washington Square Arch), 1957-1965, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Calendars, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Calendars, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Newsclippings, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Newsclippings, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New York University Law Center, 1947-1949 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New York University Library Plan, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Middle Income Housing Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Federal Public Housing and Slum Clearance Project, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tenant Relocation, Washington Square Southeast, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Tenant Relocation, Washington Square Southeast, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Housing, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Housing, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Housing: Eighth Street, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Schools, 1950-1954 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Parks and Playgrounds, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Sidewalk Cafe Legislation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Civic Executive Conference of NYC, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Post Office: Delivery Classifications, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Civil Defense, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway Project, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square Park: Plans and Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Park: Trees, 1944-1952 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Park: Planting Project, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Park: Plans and Reports, ca. 1952 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Park: Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Park: Maps, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park: Plans and Reports (May), 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square Park: Plans and Reports (July), 1958 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Park: Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square Park: Rules, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Traffic, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Traffic, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Traffic: Parking, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Traffic: Parking, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Traffic: Parking, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Traffic: Parking, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Traffic: Road Plans, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Traffic, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Traffic, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Traffic, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Traffic, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Traffic: Buses, 1957, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Traffic: Buses, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Traffic: Buses, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Traffic: Buses, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Subway Entrance Closing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Air Pollution Control: Annual Reports 1962, 1963, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Business Tax: Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Sales Tax: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Sales Tax: Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fresh Air Fund, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - New York University Community Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Police Protection, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Police Protection, 1953-1956, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Police Protection: Street Lighting, 1953-1955 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Police Protection, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Police Protection, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Police Protection: Private Patrol Study, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Police Protection, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Series VII. Annual and Special Events
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1948, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Village Art Center, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog and Correspondence, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog and Correspondence, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1961, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1963, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1965, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Art Exhibit: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog, 1968, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Art Exhibit: Correspondence, 1977, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Art Exhibit: Catalog and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1929-1952 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Celebration: Contributions, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Celebration: Correspondence, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Celebration: Contributions, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1962 (Box 22a, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1963 (Box 22a, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1964 (Box 22a, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1965 (Box 22a, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1966 (Box 22a, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1967 (Box 22a, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1976 (Box 22a, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Celebration, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Music Fund: Checking Account Book, 1959-1960 (Box 23a, Folder 9)
  - Music Fund: Bills, 1960-1962 (Box 23a, Folder 10)
  - Music Fund: Bank Records, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Music Fund: Taxes, 1959-1967 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Music Fund, 1979 (Box 23b, Folder 13)
  - Edison Plaque Reception, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Elsa G. Steinert Reception, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - United Nations Day Reception, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Committee for a Library in Jefferson Market, 1961-1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Kiwanis Club, 1975-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - MacDougall Alley Association, 1933-1941 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Village Libraries, Peoples Action Committee, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Twenty-Third Street Association, 1948-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson Market Area, Village Committee, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Waverly Block Association, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Associations & Organizations, 1958-1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Related Publications, 1920, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The 1924 Annual Banquet (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Plaque saluting New York University on its 50th Anniversary, 1982 (Box Shared University Archives 024, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Association metal box, undated (Box 32)
- Series VIII: Photographs and Drawings
  - See Photocopies in Folder 1 of this Box. (Box 25)
  - Duplicate and Oversize Material (Box 26)
  - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous WSA Activities, 1908-1919 (Flat-file-folder 4, Box 35)
  - Duplicates and Oversize Material (Box 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 28a)